call is a low-level method that is
调用是一种低层方法，适用于所有地址类型和一种
available on all address types and one
way to use it is to send ether which we
使用它的方式是发送以太币，这在我们之前的视频中已经看到
already seen in a previous video in this
video I'm gonna show you how to use the
我将向您展示如何使用call方法调用现有函数的视频
call method to call existing functions
and to call non-existing functions which
并调用会触发后备功能的不存在的功能，
would trigger the fallback function the
examples that I'm about to show you are
我将向您展示的示例不建议与之交互的方法
not to recommend a way to interact with
other contracts but knowing how to use
其他合同，但知道如何使用call方法将是一项很好的技能，
the call method will be a good skill to
have under your tool belt as a smart
身为智能合约开发者，在我们的工具之下，让我们开始吧
contract developer so let's get started
first we're going to need two contracts
首先，我们将需要两个合同
the contract that's going to be
receiving the calls and we're gonna call
接听电话，我们将致电此接听人和合同
this one receiver and the contract
that's going to be making the calls and
这将成为通话对象，我们将在内部呼叫该呼叫者
we're gonna call this one caller inside
the receiver contract we're gonna define
接收者合同，我们将定义名为foo的函数，这将是
function called foo and this will be the
function that we're gonna call from the
我们将使用以下调用从调用方合同中调用的功能
caller contract below using the call
method the function foo will take in an
方法函数foo将接受字符串的输入，并且您将结束类型
input of string and a you end the type
of inputs here are not important I just
我在此示例中选择并展示的输入的输入并不重要
picked in for this example and to show
you that we can send eater to this
您，我们可以将进食者发送到此功能，我们将宣布这一点
function we're gonna declare this
function as payable and to show you that
用作应付款功能，并向您显示call方法可以捕获回报
the call method can capture the return
value here we're gonna return a new end
值，我们将在部署合同后返回新的结局，
after we deploy the contract and
actually execute the functions we want a
实际执行我们想要的一种能够跟踪代码执行的功能
way to be able to track code execution
so we're gonna create an event that will
因此，我们将创建一个事件，以帮助我们跟踪哪些功能
help us track which functions were
called and we're gonna omit this event
调用，当在内部调用foo函数时，我们将忽略此事件
when the foo function is called inside
the event it's gonna log message dot
该事件将记录消息点发件人消息点值和消息
sender message dot value and the message
that we pass from the Foo function and
我们通过Foo功能传递的信息，只是发送给发件人的快速提醒消息
just a quick reminder message the sender
will hold address that call this
将保留调用该合同的地址，并且消息点值将保留
contract and message dot value will hold
the amount of ether that was sent and to
发送的以太币数量，并向您显示call方法可以
show you that the call method can
receive the output of the function that
接收被调用函数的输出
was called
here we're gonna add one to the input X
在这里，我们将一个添加到输入X中，然后将其返回，这样就完成了
and then return it so that completes the
function that's gonna be called when we
当我们在某个函数上使用call方法时，该函数将被调用
use the call method on a function that
exists now when we
当我们在函数上使用call方法时，现在存在
we use the call method on a function
that does not exist solidity will call
不存在稳定性的对象将调用后备功能，因此让我们定义
the fallback function so let's define
the fallback function inside the
接收者合约中的后备功能我们称为
receiver contract we call that the
visibility of the fallback function must
后备功能的可见性必须是外部的，在此示例中，
be external and for this example we're
gonna make it payable so that the
使其成为可付款项，以便后备功能可以接收和
fallback function can receive either and
similar to the function foo for
与用于调试目的的功能foo类似，我们将省略
debugging purposes we're gonna omit the
received event inside the fallback
后备功能内收到的事件，前两个值将是
function the first two values will be
the address of the color and amount of
发送的食用者的颜色和数量的地址以及该消息
eater that was sent and the message that
we're gonna log here will be fallback
我们将在此处记录将被称为fallback，以使我们感冒
was called so that completes our cold
for a contract that's gonna get called
可以通过call方法调用的合同，所以接下来让我们写
by the call method so next let's write
some code for the contract that's gonna
合同的一些代码会先将接收方合同称为双倍合同
call the receiver contract double first
let's create a function that will call
让我们创建一个函数，该函数将使用调用上面的Foo函数
the Foo function above using the call
method later after we deploy the
方法，稍后我们在这里部署合同后，我们将传递
contract here we're gonna pass in the
address of the receiver contract and
收货人合同的地址，由于我们要发送的地址是
since we're gonna send either we're
gonna declare the address as payable and
将要声明的地址为应付款，并且我们还将函数声明为
we're also gonna declare the function as
payable since we're gonna forward the
应付帐款，因为我们会将食客从我们的帐户转发至此功能
eater from our account to this function
and to the receiver contract about in a
并与接收方合同有关，在上一个视频中，我向您展示了如何发送
previous video I showed you how to send
eater to an address using the call
食用者使用这样的调用方法将地址转到默认地址
method like this by default the call
method will forward all of the gas but
方法将转发所有气体，但是如果您只想发送特定的
if you only want to send a certain
amount of gas you do it like this here
像这样做的汽油量我在告诉固体只发送5,000
I'm telling solidity to send only 5,000
gas now if you want to call function
如果您要调用后备函数以外的函数，请立即执行
other than the fallback function you
will need to pass in the parameters here
将需要在括号内以及您的方式中传递参数
inside the parentheses and the way you
would do it is like this first we need
首先要做的就是这样，我们需要调用称为ABI点的特殊功能
to call special function called ABI dot
and cold wave signature and inside the
和冷波签名，并在ABI点编码内将签名功能
ABI dot encode will signature function
we need to pass in some parameters the
我们需要传递一些参数，第一个参数是
first parameter is the signature of the
function that we want to call and the
我们要调用的函数以及创建函数签名的方法是
way to create a function signature is
similar to how you would declare a
类似于您声明具有一些细微差异的函数的方式
function with some minor differences
first you start with the function name
首先，从函数名称开始，在这种情况下，我们将调用
in this case we're going to call the
food
食物，所以我们接下来要开始食物
so here we're gonna start with food next
we declare the type of inputs that this
我们声明此函数自完整输入以来将要采用的输入类型
function is going to take since the full
function above takes a string and
上面的函数将字符串和参数作为输入，在这里我们要
argument as inputs here we're going to
declare a string followed by you end
声明一个字符串，然后结束，首先请注意没有空格
first note that there is no space
between the comma and this is important
逗号之间，这很重要接下来请注意，您需要使用联合国代替联合国
next note that instead of UN you need to
declare the full name since UN is an
声明全名，因为联合国是联合国2:56的别名，我们需要
alias for UN 2:56 here we need to
declare you into 256 and finally notice
将您声明为256，最后在这里注意，我们没有声明
here that we don't declare the type of
output the next parameters that we need
输出我们需要传递的下一个参数是实际的输入
to pass are the actual inputs that are
going to be passed to the function that
因为函数foo将被传递给我们正在调用的函数
we're calling since the function foo
takes a string and a youant as inputs
在这里输入一个字符串和一个youant作为我要传递的第一个输入的输入
here for the first input I'm gonna pass
a string value of call foo followed by a
调用foo的字符串值，后跟UN输入1 2 3，调用函数将
UN input of 1 2 3 the call function will
return to outputs the first output will
返回输出第一个输出将告诉我们函数调用是否为
tell us whether the function call was
successful or not the second output will
第二个输出是否成功将是该函数的输出
be the output of the function that was
called encoded in bytes so when we call
称为以字节为单位的编码，因此当我们调用Foo函数时，它将返回youant，因此
the Foo function it returns a youant so
here the variable data will contain the
在这里，变量数据将包含以字节为单位的youant编码，现在我们要
youant encoded in bytes now we want to
see the output of calling the function
看到通过call方法调用foo函数的输出，所以在这里
foo by the call method so here we're
gonna log two outputs and we're gonna
将记录两个输出，我们将同时记录输出成功和数据，因此
log both the outputs success and data so
that completes our function that's going
这将完成我们的功能，该功能将使用该调用来调用Foo函数
to call the Foo function using the call
method so next let's write a function
方法，所以接下来让我们编写一个函数，该函数将调用
that's gonna call function that does not
exist
存在，我们将从复制和粘贴开始
we'll start by copying and pasting this
existing code and then modify it first
现有代码，然后先对其进行修改，我们将名称更改为测试
we're gonna change the name to a test
call does not exist and just to show you
电话不存在，只是告诉您我们什么时候都不必发送
that we don't have to send either when
using the call method here we're going
在这里使用call方法，我们将删除payable关键字
to remove the payable keywords
we call that specifying the amount of
我们称指定气量是可选的，所以在这里我们要
gas is optional so here we're going to
remove this also and we're not gonna
也将其删除，我们将不发送任何食者，因此我们将删除
send any eater so we're gonna remove
this as well and we're gonna call a
这也是如此，我们将调用一个不存在的函数调用
function call does not exist which as
you can see from here does not exist
您可以从这里看到任何地方都不存在，我们可以删除
anywhere and we can remove the
parameters here since these parameters
参数，因为这些参数将作为输入传递给
will be passed as an input to the
function that we're calling and the
我们正在调用的函数以及我们正在调用的函数
function that we're calling
does not exist does not take any inputs
不存在不会接受任何输入，因此在执行此代码时，因为
so when this code is executed since the
function that we're trying to call it
我们尝试调用的函数不存在，它将调用后备
does not exist it will call the fallback
function and since the fallback function
功能，并且由于后备功能不返回任何输出，因此该数据
does not return any outputs this data
variable will be 0 bytes so that
变量将为0字节，以便完成代码以调用现有代码
completes the code to call an existing
function and a function that does not
函数和使用调用方法不存在的函数
exist using the call method let's now
deploy the contract and actually call
部署合同并实际调用这两个功能，所以在这里
these two functions so here I've
deployed the two contracts collar and
部署了两个合同项圈和接收方，我将执行测试
receiver and I'm gonna execute the test
call flu function which we'll call the
调用flu函数，我们将在接收方合同中调用flu函数，因此
flu function in the receiver contract so
I'm gonna copy the address of the
我要复制接收方合同的地址并将其粘贴到此处
receiver contract and paste it in here
so when we executed the test call foo
因此，当我们执行测试调用foo函数时，它在
function it called a function foo in the
receiver contract with the parameters
接收者契约，其中的参数称为foo，且其中的一二三
called foo and one two three inside the
function foo it emitted the event of
函数foo发出了接收到的事件，您可以在此处看到
received and you can see here in the
transaction log that the event received
接收到的事件已发出的事务日志，函数foo返回
was emitted function foo returned the
output of X plus one this output was
X的输出加一，此输出在此数据变量中捕获，并且
captured here in this data variable and
since we bought the data variable in the
由于我们在响应事件中购买了数据变量，因此您可以在此处查看
response event you can see down here
that the response event was logged and
记录了响应事件并跟踪数据，该数据是出埃及记
dog the data this data is an exodus mo
notation and down here I opened the
表示法和此处，我在网络浏览器中打开了JavaScript控制台
JavaScript console in the web browser
and decoded the hexadecimal data and you
并解码了十六进制数据，您可以看到返回了
can see that a return
124 we passed 123 as input and the
124我们将123作为输入传递，并且函数foo返回123加1，其中
function foo returned 123 plus 1 which
is equal to 124 and this data down below
等于124，此下方的数据等于124，紧挨着
here is equal to 124 and next to the
small notation next I'm gonna walk you
小写法接下来，当我们调用时，我将带您逐步执行代码
through the code execution when we call
test call does not exist so again I'm
测试电话不存在，所以我要再次复制接收方的地址
gonna copy the address of the receiver
contract paste it in here and call test
合同将其粘贴到此处，然后调用测试调用不存在，让我们检查一下
call does not exist and let's check the
transaction log as you can see from the
从事件狗可以看到的事务日志，回退功能是
event dog the fallback function was
called and they returned the data of Geo
调用后，他们返回了地理字节的数据，因此发生的情况是当我们调用
bytes so what happened was when we call
the test call does not exist function it
测试调用不存在功能，它试图调用不存在的功能
tried to call a function that does not
exist and since the function does not
存在，并且由于该函数不存在，因此接收器内部不存在
exist does not exist inside the receiver
contract solidity called the fallback
合约稳固性称为后备功能，它使用
function and it bout the event with the
message fall back was called after the
消息回退被调用后，回退被称为返回0个字节，并且
fallback was called a return 0 bytes and
we saw in the transaction though that 0
我们在事务中看到，尽管响应事件中有0个字节是狗
bytes was dog inside the response event
so in summary you can use the call
因此，总的来说，如果
method to call other functions if the
function being called does not exist
被调用的函数不存在，则回退函数将是
then the fallback function will be
called now this function is not to
现在调用此功能不是建议一种方法来调用所有
recommend a way to call all the
functions since it's very easy to mess
函数，因为很容易弄乱函数签名，因此
up the function signatures so for
example even though if you know that the
即使您知道如果弄乱了函数foo的存在，该示例
function foo exists if you mess up the
function signature then the fallback
函数签名，然后将调用后备函数，仅此而已
function will be called well that's all
I got for this video if you have any
如果您有任何反馈或疑问，请在
feedback or questions let me know in the
comments below have a good night and
以下评论度过了一个美好的夜晚，下个视频再见
I'll see you in the next video